Guide to the Floyd Millard Riddick Papers, 1909-2000 RL.01088
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2007-0165), 1928-2000
  - VHS Cassettes
    - The Library's commemoration of the 500,000th volume, April 1997 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
    - At the Williamsburg Practicum, June 1992 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
    - CSPAN Interview, May 1986 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
    - CSPAN Interview, October 1986 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
    - Speaking at Bob Jones University, October 1994 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Audiocassettes
    - Oral History interview, June 13, 1990 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
    - Radio Interview in South Africa (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
    - American Institute of Parliamentarians: Riddick: Essence of Bylaws (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Mini VHS
    - No title (TC-30 EHG tape) (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
- Accession (2008-0179) 1933-1992
  The addition (2008-0179) (100 items; 0.6 lin. ft.; 1933-1993) contains publications, academic materials, clippings, correspondence, and miscellaneous materials, including a copy of the Senate Resolution 443 that declared Riddick as the Parliamentarian Emeritus of the U.S. Senate.
  This addition has been interfiled with Accession (2007-0165), Box 1.
  - Publications, 1978-1993 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Clippings (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Academics, 1933-1955 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1992 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous drafts and photocopies (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Senate Resolution 443 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
- Accession (2014-0073) 1937-2007
  The addition (2014-0073) (140 items; 0.2 lin. ft; 1937-2007) contains publications, biographical materials, clippings, correspondence, two print materials, photographs, and several miscellaneous drafs and documents. Publications include Riddick's descriptions of general Senate procedures and protocol,including those during impeachment. The bulk of the photographs, correspondence, and clippings are from the end of Riddick's life (1980-2000).
  - Biographical publications, 1966-2000 and undated (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Clippings (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Correspondence, 1938-2007 and undated (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - "Founders of the Cosmos Club" (1966 print) (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Miscellaneous drafts (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Photographs (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - "Point of Opinion" (2004 print) (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Publications, 1937-1985 (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
- Accession (2017-0039), 1937-1997 and undated
  Scope and Contents
  This addition includes documents pertaining to the American Institute of Parlimentarians, correspondence from Duke University, manuscript drafts (including a few pages of Riddick's remininscences of President Richard M. Nixon), and photographs from President Jimmy Carter's inaugeration.
  - American Institute of Parliamentarians, Leo G. Athans, 1996-1997 (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Biographical information and passport, 1937-1980s and undated (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Conversation with former Senator Payne, 1976 August 13 (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Lecture notes in American foreign relations, 1938 and undated (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Letters from Duke regarding gifts to the Law School and Perkins Library, 1989-1997 (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Manuscript draft by George Galloway: History of the House Representatives, undated (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Manuscript draft, Comments on notes and subjects, undated (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Manuscript draft, Notes on Nixon, undated (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Inaugural Ceremonies album, 1977 (Box Acc. 17/39: Box 1)